<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml version="2.0">

<category>
    <pattern>HELLO</pattern>
    <template>
    Hello! I'm the Career Recommendation Chatbot for XMUM students. You can ask about:<br/>
    - Majors and departments (e.g., "What majors are in Informatics?")<br/>
    - Career options by major (e.g., "What careers for software engineering")<br/>
    - Detailed career information (e.g., "Details about a backend developer")<br/>
    - Cross-disciplinary options (e.g., "Careers for both arts and science")<br/>
    - Career preparation (e.g., "How to prepare a resume")<br/>
    - Career Services Office information
    </template>
</category>
<category>
    <pattern>HI</pattern>
    <template><srai>HELLO</srai></template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>WHAT MAJORS ARE IN *</pattern>
    <template>
        <think><set name="department"><star/></set></think>
        <condition name="department">
            <li value="INFORMATICS">School of Informatics majors:<br/>Computer Science,<br/>Software Engineering,<br/>Artificial Intelligence,<br/>Data Science,<br/>Cybersecurity,<br/>Digital Media Technology.</li>
            <li value="ECONOMICS AND MANAGEMENT">School of Economics &amp; Management majors:<br/>E-commerce,<br/>International Business,<br/>Accounting,<br/>Finance.</li>
            <li value="HUMANITIES AND COMMUNICATION">School of Humanities &amp; Communication majors:<br/>Journalism,<br/>Advertising,<br/>Chinese Language &amp; Literature,<br/>English.</li>
            <li value="TRADITIONAL CHINESE MEDICINE">School of TCM majors:<br/>Chinese Medicine.</li>
            <li value="ENGINEERING">School of Engineering majors:<br/>Electronic Information Engineering,<br/>Chemical Engineering,<br/>New Energy Science.</li>
            <li value="MARINE AND EARTH SCIENCES">School of Marine &amp; Earth Sciences majors:<br/>Marine Science,<br/>Marine Technology.</li>
            <li value="MATHEMATICAL SCIENCES">School of Mathematical Sciences majors:<br/>Mathematics,<br/>Physics.</li>
            <li>Please specify a department, for example: INFORMATICS,ENGINEERING , or ECONOMICS AND MANAGEMENT.</li>
        </condition>
    </template>
</category>

<!-- CAREERS BY MAJOR -->
<category>
    <pattern>CAREERS FOR *</pattern>
    <template>
        <think><set name="major"><star/></set></think>
        <condition name="major">
            <!-- School of Informatics -->
            <li value="COMPUTER SCIENCE">Computer Science careers include: Backend Developer, Frontend Developer, Full-Stack Developer, Mobile App Developer, DevOps Engineer, Game Programmer, Embedded Systems Engineer, Cloud Solutions Architect, Database Administrator.</li>
            <li value="CST"><srai>WHAT CAREERS FOR COMPUTER SCIENCE</srai></li>
            <li value="SOFTWARE ENGINEERING">Software Engineering careers include: Backend Developer, Frontend Developer, Full-Stack Developer, Mobile App Developer, DevOps Engineer, SDET, Game Programmer, Cloud Solutions Architect.</li>
            <li value="SE"><srai>WHAT CAREERS FOR SOFTWARE ENGINEERING</srai></li>
            <li value="ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE">AI careers include: Machine Learning Engineer, AI Research Scientist, NLP Engineer, Computer Vision Engineer, Data Scientist.</li>
            <li value="AIT"><srai>WHAT CAREERS FOR ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE</srai></li>
            <li value="DATA SCIENCE">Data Science careers include: Data Analyst, Data Scientist, Data Engineer, Machine Learning Engineer, BI Analyst.</li>
            <li value="CYBERSECURITY">Cybersecurity careers include: Penetration Tester, Security Analyst, Security Architect, Digital Forensics Analyst.</li>
            <li value="DIGITAL MEDIA TECHNOLOGY">Digital Media careers include: UI Designer, UX Designer, UX Researcher, 3D Modeler, VR/AR Developer, Game Designer, Motion Graphics Designer, Technical Artist.</li>
            <!-- Economics & Management -->
            <li value="E-COMMERCE">E-commerce careers include: E-commerce Operations Specialist, Digital Marketing Manager, SEO/SEM Specialist, Social Media Manager, Content Marketing Strategist, BI Analyst.</li>
            <li value="INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS">International Business careers include: Supply Chain Analyst, International Trade Specialist, Business Development Manager, Management Consultant, Market Research Analyst.</li>
            <li value="ACCOUNTING">Accounting careers include: Auditor, Management Accountant, Tax Consultant, Forensic Accountant, Internal Auditor, Financial Controller.</li>
            <li value="FINANCE">Finance careers include: Investment Banking Analyst, Risk Manager, Wealth Management Advisor, Credit Analyst, Quantitative Analyst, Compliance Officer.</li>
            <!-- Humanities & Communication -->
            <li value="JOURNALISM">Journalism careers include: Broadcast Journalist, Digital Content Editor, Public Relations Specialist, Corporate Communications Manager, Event Manager.</li>
            <li value="ADVERTISING">Advertising careers include: Creative Copywriter, Art Director, Digital Marketing Manager, Social Media Manager, Content Marketing Strategist, Media Planner.</li>
            <li value="CHINESE LANGUAGE">Chinese Language careers include: Translator, Interpreter, Publishing Editor, Localization Specialist, Chinese Language Teacher.</li>
            <li value="ENGLISH">English careers include: Technical Writer, Translator, Interpreter, ESL Teacher, Digital Content Editor, Content Marketing Strategist.</li>
            <!-- Traditional Chinese Medicine -->
            <li value="CHINESE MEDICINE">Chinese Medicine careers include: Acupuncturist, Herbalist, TCM Health Consultant, TCM Researcher.</li>
            <!-- Engineering -->
            <li value="ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING">Electronic Engineering careers include: Electronics Hardware Engineer, Telecommunications Engineer, Control Systems Engineer, Semiconductor Engineer.</li>
            <li value="CHEMICAL ENGINEERING">Chemical Engineering careers include: Process Engineer, Product Development Scientist, Safety Engineer, Materials Engineer.</li>
            <li value="NEW ENERGY">New Energy careers include: Solar Energy Engineer, Energy Analyst, Materials Engineer.</li>
            <!-- Marine & Earth Sciences -->
            <li value="MARINE SCIENCE">Marine Science careers include: Physical Oceanographer, Marine Chemist, Marine Biologist, Aquaculture Manager, Marine Conservationist, Marine Policy Advisor.</li>
            <li value="MARINE TECHNOLOGY">Marine Technology careers include: Hydrographic Surveyor, Marine Equipment Engineer, Underwater Robotics Specialist.</li>
            <!-- Mathematical Sciences -->
            <li value="MATHEMATICS">Mathematics careers include: Actuary, Statistician, Operations Research Analyst, Quantitative Analyst, Data Scientist.</li>
            <li value="PHYSICS">Physics careers include: Medical Physicist, Astrophysicist, Semiconductor Engineer, Materials Engineer, Quantitative Analyst.</li>
            <li>
                I don't recognize that major. Please try one of these:
                COMPUTER SCIENCE, SOFTWARE ENGINEERING, AI, DATA SCIENCE, CYBERSECURITY,
                DIGITAL MEDIA TECHNOLOGY, E-COMMERCE, INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS, ACCOUNTING, FINANCE,
                JOURNALISM, ADVERTISING, CHINESE LANGUAGE, ENGLISH, CHINESE MEDICINE,
                ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING, CHEMICAL ENGINEERING, NEW ENERGY,
                MARINE SCIENCE, MARINE TECHNOLOGY, MATHEMATICS, PHYSICS.
            </li>
        </condition>
    </template>
</category>
<category>
    <pattern>WHAT CAREERS FOR *</pattern>
    <template><srai>CAREERS FOR <star/></srai></template>
</category>

<!-- DETAILED CAREER INFORMATION -->
<category>
    <pattern>DETAILS ABOUT *</pattern>
    <template>
        <think><set name="career"><star/></set></think>
        <condition name="career">
            <!-- School of Informatics Careers -->
            <li value="BACKEND DEVELOPER">
                <b>Backend Developer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> As the architects of the digital world, backend developers design, build, and maintain all server-side logic that users don't see. They handle data storage, ensure smooth server-frontend communication, and create robust APIs.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> API development, database optimization, system security, Python, Java, Go.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Software Engineering, Computer Science.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Data Structures, Algorithm Design, Database Systems, Operating Systems, Computer Networks.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Junior Backend Engineer → Senior Backend Engineer → System Architect / Tech Lead.
                <br/><b>Industries:</b> Tech companies, Fintech, E-commerce.
                <br/><b>Salary:</b> RM 4,000 - RM 15,000/month.
            </li>
            <li value="FRONTEND DEVELOPER">
                <b>Frontend Developer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Frontend developers are the direct creators of a digital product's look and feel. They translate visual blueprints from designers into dynamic, interactive interfaces that users can click, scroll, and engage with.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Vue, Angular, UI/UX principles.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Software Engineering, Computer Science, Digital Media Technology.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Web Application Development, Human-Computer Interaction, JavaScript Programming, Mobile Application Development.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Junior Frontend Engineer → Senior Frontend Engineer → Frontend Architect / UI Engineering Lead.
                <br/><b>Industries:</b> Tech, E-commerce, Media, any company with a web presence.
            </li>
            <li value="FULL STACK DEVELOPER">
                <b>Full-Stack Developer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Often called the "Swiss Army Knife" of the tech world, full-stack developers master both frontend (user interface) and backend (server and database) technologies. They can independently build and deploy a complete web application from scratch.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Both frontend and backend technologies, database management, DevOps principles.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Software Engineering, Computer Science.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Web Application Development, Database Systems, Software Architecture, Cloud Computing.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Full-Stack Engineer → Senior Full-Stack Engineer → Solutions Architect / Technical Co-founder.
            </li>
            <li value="MOBILE APP DEVELOPER">
                <b>Mobile App Developer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> In an age where everyone has a smartphone, mobile app developers are key players connecting users to digital services. They specialize in designing, developing, and optimizing apps for iOS (using Swift/Objective-C) or Android (using Kotlin/Java).
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Swift/Kotlin, mobile UI/UX, API integration, performance optimization.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Software Engineering, Computer Science.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Mobile Application Development, Object-Oriented Programming, Data Structures, Human-Computer Interaction.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Junior App Developer → Senior App Developer → Mobile Tech Lead.
            </li>
            <li value="DEVOPS ENGINEER">
                <b>DevOps Engineer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> DevOps engineers revolutionize the efficiency and quality of software development. They break down the barriers between Development (Dev) and Operations (Ops) by building automated testing, continuous integration, and continuous deployment (CI/CD) pipelines.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> CI/CD tools (Jenkins, GitLab), cloud platforms (AWS, Azure), containerization (Docker, Kubernetes), scripting.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Software Engineering, Computer Science, Cybersecurity.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Operating Systems, Computer Networks, Cloud Computing, Scripting Languages (Python/Bash).
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> DevOps Engineer → Senior DevOps Engineer → DevOps Architect.
            </li>
            <li value="SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ENGINEER IN TEST">
                <b>SDET Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> SDETs are the ultimate guardians of software quality, but their weapon of choice is code. Unlike traditional testers, they write automated test scripts, build testing frameworks, and develop tools to efficiently and comprehensively detect software defects.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Automation testing frameworks (Selenium, Cypress), programming, test planning.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Software Engineering, Computer Science.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Principles of Software Engineering, Software Testing and Quality Assurance, Programming, Database Systems.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Test Engineer → Automation Test Developer → Test Manager / QA Director.
            </li>
            <li value="GAME PROGRAMMER">
                <b>Game Programmer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Game programmers are the magicians who turn imaginative game designs into reality. They write the code for everything in the game world, including the graphics engine, physics simulation, character AI, and network synchronization.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> C++, game engines (Unity, Unreal), computer graphics, physics, linear algebra.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Software Engineering, Computer Science, Digital Media Technology.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Programming (C++), Algorithm Design, Computer Graphics, Fundamentals of Game Development.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Junior Game Programmer → Engine/Graphics Programmer → Lead Programmer.
            </li>
            <li value="EMBEDDED SYSTEMS ENGINEER">
                <b>Embedded Systems Engineer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Embedded engineers are the cornerstone of the Internet of Things (IoT) world. They design and develop specialized software and hardware systems within various smart devices (like smart home appliances, automotive electronics, and wearables).
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> C/C++, microcontrollers, real-time operating systems (RTOS), hardware design.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Electronic Information Engineering, Computer Science.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Microprocessor and Microcontroller, Operating Systems, C/C++ Programming, Digital Logic Design.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Embedded Engineer → Firmware Engineer → Embedded Systems Architect.
            </li>
            <li value="CLOUD SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT">
                <b>Cloud Solutions Architect Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The lead designer for a company's cloud computing strategy. They master platforms like AWS and Azure to design secure, reliable, and cost-effective cloud IT architectures based on business needs.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> AWS/Azure/GCP, security architecture, network design, cost optimization, automation.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Software Engineering, Computer Science, Cybersecurity.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Cloud Computing, Computer Networks, Database Systems, Information Security.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Cloud Engineer → Cloud Architect → Chief Technology Officer (CTO).
                <br/><b>Industries:</b> Tech, Finance, Enterprise Solutions.
                <br/><b>Salary:</b> RM 12,000 - RM 25,000/month.
            </li>
            <li value="MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER">
                <b>Machine Learning Engineer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> ML Engineers bridge the gap between AI research and practical application. They take the algorithmic models validated by data scientists, engineer and optimize them, and deploy them into production environments to handle massive real-time data.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Python, TensorFlow/PyTorch, MLOps, software engineering principles.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Artificial Intelligence, Data Science, Software Engineering.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Python Programming, Software Engineering, Big Data Management.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> ML Engineer → Senior ML Engineer → AI Tech Lead.
            </li>
            <li value="AI RESEARCH SCIENTIST">
                <b>AI Research Scientist Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Pioneers in exploring new AI frontiers, inventing novel algorithms or models. Often work in top tech firms or academia, requiring top-tier math, coding skills, and curiosity.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Machine learning theory, deep learning, advanced mathematics, Python, research methodology.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Artificial Intelligence, Computer Science, Data Science (Master’s/PhD usually required).
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Advanced Algorithms, Deep Learning Theory, Mathematical Modeling, Advanced Statistics.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Research Assistant → Research Scientist → Chief Scientist.
            </li>
            <li value="NLP ENGINEER">
                <b>NLP Engineer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Builds systems for machines to understand/generate human language. Combines linguistics, CS, and ML.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> NLP toolkits, machine learning, deep learning, Python, linguistics basics.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Artificial Intelligence, Computer Science.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Natural Language Processing, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Linguistics.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> NLP Engineer → NLP Expert → Conversational AI Architect.
            </li>
            <li value="COMPUTER VISION ENGINEER">
                <b>Computer Vision Engineer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Develops algorithms to give machines the ability to “see” (face/object detection, AR effects, etc.).
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Computer vision algorithms, deep learning, Python, OpenCV, linear algebra.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Artificial Intelligence, Digital Media Technology, Computer Science.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Computer Vision, Digital Image Processing, Deep Learning, Linear Algebra.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> CV Engineer → Senior CV Engineer → Vision Tech Lead.
            </li>
            <li value="DATA ANALYST">
                <b>Data Analyst Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The data detective — cleans, analyzes, visualizes data for clear insights to guide decisions.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> SQL, Python, statistics, data visualization, BI tools.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Data Science, E-commerce, Mathematics.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Statistics, Python Programming, Database Systems, Data Visualization, Business Intelligence.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Data Analyst → Senior Data Analyst → Data Analytics Manager.
            </li>
            <li value="DATA SCIENTIST">
                <b>Data Scientist Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Mines data for business insights, builds predictive models.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Machine learning, statistics, Python, big data tools.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Data Science, Artificial Intelligence.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Machine Learning, Statistics, Algorithm Design, Big Data Management.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Data Scientist → Senior Data Scientist → Chief Data Scientist.
            </li>
            <li value="DATA ENGINEER">
                <b>Data Engineer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Designs and maintains data pipelines and warehouses to feed analytics and data science.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Big data frameworks, SQL, data warehousing, cloud platforms.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Data Science, Software Engineering.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Big Data Management, Database Systems, Cloud Computing, Software Engineering.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Data Engineer → Big Data Architect → Data Platform Director.
            </li>
            <li value="CYBERSECURITY ANALYST">
                <b>Cybersecurity Analyst Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The frontline sentinel of digital defense. Works in a Security Operations Center, monitoring network traffic and logs 24/7, analyzing threats, and launching rapid incident responses to minimize damage.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Network security, information security, incident response, digital forensics, security tools.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Cybersecurity.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Information Security, Network Security, Incident Response, Digital Forensics.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Junior Security Analyst → Senior Security Analyst → SOC Manager.
            </li>
            <li value="PENETRATION TESTER">
            <b>Penetration Tester / Ethical Hacker Details:</b>
            <br/><b>Role:</b> The "white hat" hacker. Authorized by companies to think and act like a malicious hacker in order to identify and help fix security vulnerabilities before real attackers can exploit them. Protects digital assets by simulating cyberattacks on websites, apps, and networks.
            <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Penetration testing, ethical hacking, network security, web security, cryptography.
            <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Cybersecurity.
            <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Ethical Hacking and Penetration Testing, Network Security, Web Security, Cryptography.
            <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Penetration Tester → Senior Penetration Tester → Security Consultant.
            </li>
            <li value="TECH PRODUCT MANAGER">
                <b>Tech Product Manager Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "CEO of the product". Defines product vision, researches user needs and market competition, writes PRD, and leads the team to deliver. Acts as the bridge between users, technology, and business.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Product visioning, user research, project management, PRD writing, cross-functional leadership.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Any School of Information major combined with business knowledge.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Human-Computer Interaction, Software Engineering, Marketing Principles, Data Analysis.
            </li>
            <li value="USER INTERFACE DESIGNER">
                <b>User Interface Designer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The “stylist” of digital products. Designs every icon, button, color palette, and font layout to align with brand image while ensuring visual appeal and usability.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Visual communication, graphic design tools(Photoshop, Figma), typography, color theory.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Digital Media Technology, Advertising.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Visual Communication, Computer-Aided Design(Photoshop, Figma), Typography, Digital Imaging.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> UI Designer → Senior UI Designer → Visual Design Lead.
            </li>
            <li value="USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER">
                <b>User Experience Designer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "architect of user experience". Designs information architecture, user flows, and prototypes to ensure ease of use, efficiency, and satisfaction.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> UX research, wireframing, prototyping, usability testing.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Digital Media Technology.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Human-Computer Interaction, User Experience Design, Interaction Design, Psychology of Design (elective).
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> UX Designer → Senior UX Designer → UX Strategist/Lead.
            </li>
            <li value="3D MODELER">
                <b>3D Modeler Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "sculptor" of virtual worlds. Turns 2D concept art into 3D models for characters, props, vehicles, or buildings using professional 3D software.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> 3D modeling, texturing, shading, rendering.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Digital Media Technology.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> 3D Animation, Digital Modeling and Rendering, Texturing and Shading.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> 3D Modeler → Character/Environment Artist → Art Director.
            </li>
            <li value="GAME DESIGNER">
                <b>Game Designer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "master designer" of game projects. Designs core gameplay, world-building, story, levels, balance, and player progression.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Game mechanics design, storytelling, level design, game scripting.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Digital Media Technology.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Game Design and Development, Level Design, Scripting for Games, Psychology of Play.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Level Designer/System Designer → Lead Designer → Producer.
            </li>
            <li value="E-COMMERCE OPERATIONS SPECIALIST">
                <b>E-commerce Operations Specialist Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The “store manager” of online shops. Handles daily operations including product listing, page optimization, promotions, order processing, inventory management, and customer service. Requires familiarity with platform rules and basic data analysis skills to monitor sales performance.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> E-commerce platform operations, promotion planning, data analysis, customer service.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> E-commerce, International Business.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> E-commerce, Digital Marketing, Supply Chain Management, Customer Relationship Management.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Operations Assistant → Operations Specialist → Store Manager/Operations Supervisor.
            </li>
            <li value="DIGITAL MARKETING MANAGER">
                <b>Digital Marketing Manager Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The “chief strategist” for online customer acquisition. Manages all digital channels (SEO/SEM, social media, content marketing, email marketing), formulates strategy and budget, and is accountable for ROI.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Digital marketing strategy, analytics, budget management, campaign optimization.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> E-commerce, Advertising.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Digital Marketing, Marketing Analytics, Consumer Behavior, Integrated Marketing Communication.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Digital Marketing Executive → Digital Marketing Manager → Chief Marketing Officer (CMO).
            </li>
            <li value="SEO/SEM SPECIALIST">
                <b>SEO/SEM Specialist Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The “traffic wizard” of digital marketing. SEO experts optimize website content and technology to improve organic search rankings, while SEM experts manage paid ads to attract precise customer segments.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> SEO/SEM techniques, keyword research, ad campaign management, web analytics.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> E-commerce, Advertising.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Digital Marketing, Data Analytics, Web Analytics, Consumer Behavior.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> SEO/SEM Specialist → Growth Manager → Digital Marketing Director.
            </li>
            <li value="AUDITOR">
                <b>Auditor Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "economic police" of capital markets. Works independently to rigorously verify if financial reports of public companies fairly reflect their operations, safeguarding investors and market confidence.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Auditing, financial reporting, ethics, regulatory compliance.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Accounting.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Auditing and Assurance, Financial Accounting and Reporting, Taxation, Corporate Law.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Audit Assistant → Senior Auditor → Audit Manager → Partner.
            </li>
            <li value="TAX CONSULTANT">
                <b>Tax Consultant Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> A tax law expert who helps individuals and businesses plan taxes legally and efficiently, minimizing tax burden and handling filings and audits.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Tax planning, compliance, financial accounting, business law.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Accounting.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Taxation, Advanced Taxation, Business Law, Financial Accounting.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Tax Assistant → Tax Consultant → Tax Manager → Tax Partner.
            </li>
            <li value="MANAGEMENT ACCOUNTANT">
                <b>Management Accountant Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "financial advisor" within a company. Focuses on budgeting, cost analysis, and investment evaluation to support executive decisions.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Cost analysis, budgeting, financial strategy, business decision support.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Accounting.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Management Accounting, Financial Management, Cost Accounting, Strategic Management.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Accountant → Financial Analyst → Finance Manager → CFO.
            </li>
            <li value="INVESTMENT BANKING ANALYST">
                <b>Investment Banking Analyst Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Entry-level role at top investment banks. Conducts industry research, builds financial models, and prepares presentations for M&amp;A, IPOs, and capital transactions.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Financial modeling, corporate finance, analytical thinking, presentation skills.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Finance, Accounting.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Corporate Finance, Investment Analysis, Financial Modeling, Mergers and Acquisitions.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Analyst → Associate/Manager → VP → Managing Director (MD).
            </li>
            <li value="RISK MANAGER">
                <b>Risk Manager Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "braking system" of financial institutions. Identifies, assesses, and manages risks like market, credit, or operational risks; designs strategies to mitigate them.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Risk analysis, financial instruments, quantitative analysis, regulatory compliance.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Finance.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Derivatives and Risk Management, Financial Econometrics, Investment Analysis, Statistics.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Risk Analyst → Risk Manager → Chief Risk Officer (CRO).
            </li>
            <li value="WEALTH MANAGEMENT ADVISOR">
                <b>Wealth Management Advisor Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "private financial steward" for high-net-worth clients. Provides customized financial plans covering investments, tax optimization, retirement, and wealth transfer.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Financial planning, portfolio management, client relationship, tax strategy.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Finance.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Portfolio Management, Investment Analysis, Personal Financial Planning, Behavioral Finance.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Relationship Manager → Wealth Advisor → Private Banker.
            </li>
            <li value="QUANT">
                <b>Quantitative Analyst Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Uses advanced mathematics, statistics, and programming to design algorithmic trading strategies or price complex financial derivatives.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Mathematical modeling, statistical analysis, programming (Python, C++), quantitative finance.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Mathematics and Applied Mathematics, Finance, Physics.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Financial Mathematics, Stochastic Processes, Econometrics, Advanced Programming.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Quant Analyst → Senior Quant → Quantitative Portfolio Manager.
            </li>
            <li value="BROADCAST JOURNALIST">
                <b>Broadcast Journalist Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The storyteller and presenter of TV and radio news. Gathers, verifies, writes, and delivers news with clarity and impact for viewers and listeners.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Reporting, script writing, on-camera presence, voice delivery.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Journalism.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Broadcast Journalism, News Writing and Reporting, Media Law and Ethics, Voice and Diction.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Reporter → Anchor/Host → Producer.
            </li>
            <li value="DIGITAL CONTENT EDITOR">
                <b>Digital Content Editor Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The content manager of online media. Plans, writes, edits, and publishes content for websites, apps, and social media, leveraging SEO and analytics to maximize impact.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Writing, editing, SEO, data analysis, content strategy.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Journalism, Advertising, English.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Web Writing and Editing, Content Marketing, SEO Principles, Social Media Management.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Content Editor → Senior Editor → Content Manager/Chief Editor.
            </li>
            <li value="PUBLIC RELATIONS SPECIALIST">
                <b>Public Relations Specialist Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "image ambassador" of an organization or brand. Manages media relations, PR campaigns, press releases, and social media to build a positive public image and handle crises.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> PR strategy, media relations, communication, crisis management.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Advertising, Journalism.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Public Relations, Media Writing, Corporate Communication, Crisis Management.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> PR Assistant → PR Specialist → PR Manager → PR Director.
            </li>
            <li value="CREATIVE COPYWRITER">
                <b>Creative Copywriter Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "soul writer" of advertising. Crafts precise, moving, and insightful text to form the core of ads—from slogans to video scripts to viral social media posts—aimed at winning consumers' hearts and driving action.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Copywriting, creative thinking, brand storytelling, consumer psychology.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Advertising, English, Chinese Language and Literature.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Copywriting, Advertising Creativity, Brand Storytelling, Consumer Behavior.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Copywriter → Senior Copywriter → Creative Lead → Creative Director.
            </li>
            <li value="ART DIRECTOR">
                <b>Art Director Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "visual commander" of advertising. Works with copywriters to transform ideas into compelling visual expressions, guiding designers, photographers, illustrators, and directors to deliver impactful and precise imagery.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Visual design, art direction, creative leadership, communication.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Advertising, Digital Media Technology.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Advertising Design, Visual Communication, Art Direction, Computer-Aided Design.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Designer → Art Director → Creative Lead → Creative Director.
            </li>
            <li value="TRANSLATOR">
                <b>Translator Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "messenger" of cross-cultural written communication. Goes beyond word-for-word translation to convey the true meaning, context, and style in the target language for diverse materials from literature to legal contracts.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Bilingual proficiency, cultural understanding, writing, editing.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> English, Chinese Language and Literature.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Translation Theory and Practice, Advanced Writing, Comparative Literature, Linguistics.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Junior Translator → Senior Translator → Proofreader/Translation Project Manager.
            </li>
            <li value="INTERPRETER">
                <b>Interpreter Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "fast-acting language bridge." Provides real-time spoken translation in international meetings, business negotiations, and legal proceedings, demanding top bilingual skills, memory, composure, and broad knowledge.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Interpreting, public speaking, listening, cross-cultural communication.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> English, Chinese Language and Literature.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Interpreting Skills, Public Speaking, Advanced Listening and Speaking, Cross-cultural Communication.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Escort Interpreter → Conference Interpreter → Simultaneous Interpreter.
            </li>
            <li value="CHINESE LANGUAGE TEACHER">
                <b>Chinese Language Teacher Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> A "cultural ambassador" spreading Chinese language and culture globally. Designs engaging activities to teach listening, speaking, reading, and writing, while introducing Chinese culture to diverse learners.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Language teaching, cultural communication, instructional design.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Chinese Language and Literature.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Teaching Chinese as a Second Language, Modern Chinese Language, Chinese Culture, Linguistics.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Teacher → Teaching Leader → Course Coordinator.
            </li>
            <li value="ENGLISH TEACHER">
                <b>English Teacher (ESL) Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "key" helping non-native speakers access the English-speaking world. Creates immersive environments and uses second-language teaching methods to build learners' interest and confidence.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> TESL methods, communication, classroom management.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> English.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Teaching English as a Second Language (TESL), Phonetics and Phonology, Syntax, Sociolinguistics.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Teacher → Senior Teacher/Trainer → Academic Director.
            </li>
            <li value="TCM HEALTH CONSULTANT">
                <b>TCM Health Consultant Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> A modern practitioner of the "preventive treatment" philosophy in TCM. Provides personalized wellness plans including dietary therapy, exercise, emotional guidance, and seasonal health tips.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> TCM diagnosis, health planning, client communication.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Traditional Chinese Medicine.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> TCM Health Preservation, Dietetics of Chinese Medicine, TCM Basic Theory, Psychology of TCM.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Health Consultant → Wellness Center Director → Brand Health Advisor.
            </li>
            <li value="TCM RESEARCHER">
                <b>TCM Researcher Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The scientific force advancing TCM globally. Uses pharmacology, molecular biology, and data science to study active ingredients, mechanisms of formulas, and acupuncture's neurobiological basis.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Research, data analysis, academic writing.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Traditional Chinese Medicine (typically requires MSc/PhD).
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> TCM Research Methodology, Pharmacology, Molecular Biology, Statistics.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Research Assistant → Associate Researcher → Principal Investigator (PI).
            </li>
            <li value="ELECTRONICS HARDWARE ENGINEER">
                <b>Electronics Hardware Engineer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "heart creator" of electronics, responsible for designing, developing, and testing PCBs and selecting microprocessors, sensors, and chips for devices from smartphones to satellites.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Circuit design, PCB development, hardware debugging, component selection.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Electronics and Information Engineering.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Circuit Theory, Digital Logic Design, Analog Electronics, Microprocessor.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Hardware Engineer → Senior Hardware Engineer → Hardware Architect.
            </li>
            <li value="TELECOMMUNICATIONS ENGINEER">
                <b>Telecommunications Engineer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "network builder" of the information society, designing, deploying, and maintaining systems that support global communication from 5G networks to submarine cables.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Communication systems, signal processing, RF engineering, network planning.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Electronics and Information Engineering.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Communication Principles, Signals and Systems, Electromagnetic Fields and Waves, Digital Signal Processing.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Telecommunications Engineer → RF Engineer → Network Planning Specialist.
            </li>
            <li value="PROCESS ENGINEER">
                <b>Process Engineer (Chemical) Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "process optimization master" in chemical plants, designing safe, efficient, cost-effective processes for large-scale production and continuously improving operations.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Process design, data analysis, safety management, optimization.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Chemical Engineering and Technology.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Chemical Process Principles, Thermodynamics, Heat and Mass Transfer, Reactor Design.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Process Engineer → Senior Process Engineer → Production Manager / Plant Manager.
            </li>
            <li value="PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT SCIENTIST">
                <b>Product Development Scientist (Chemical) Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "new material creator" who designs formulas and runs experiments to develop chemical products like eco-friendly coatings or high-performance battery materials.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> R&amp;D, chemical formulation, laboratory testing, innovation.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Chemical Engineering and Technology.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Organic Chemistry, Polymer Science, Product Design and Development, Reaction Engineering.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> R&amp;D Scientist → Project Lead → R&amp;D Manager.
            </li>
            <li value="SAFETY ENGINEER">
                <b>Safety Engineer (Chemical) Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The "risk control officer" who identifies hazards like fire or toxic leaks, designs safety systems, and prepares emergency plans to protect life and environment.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Risk assessment, process safety, emergency planning, compliance.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Chemical Engineering and Technology.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Chemical Process Safety, Risk Assessment, Industrial Regulations, Thermodynamics.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Safety Engineer → EHS Manager → Regional EHS Director.
            </li>
            <li value="SOLAR ENERGY ENGINEER">
                <b>Solar Energy Engineer Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> A key player in the green energy revolution, responsible for solar plant site selection, design, equipment selection, construction management, and grid connection.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Solar system design, power electronics, energy storage, project management.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> New Energy Science and Engineering.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Solar Energy Engineering, Semiconductor Physics, Power Electronics, Energy Storage.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Solar Engineer → Project Manager → Renewable Energy Specialist.
            </li>
            <li value="MARINE BIOLOGIST">
                <b>Marine Biologist Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> An explorer of marine life, studying the physiology, behavior, genetics, and ecology of marine organisms from plankton to whales, contributing to biodiversity conservation and sustainable fisheries.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Marine species research, data analysis, fieldwork, biodiversity monitoring.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Marine Science.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Marine Biology, Ecology, Marine Microbiology, Fisheries Science.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Research Assistant → Marine Biologist → Chief Scientist / Professor.
            </li>
            <li value="MARINE CONSERVATIONIST">
                <b>Marine Conservationist Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> A guardian of marine ecosystems, working in NGOs or government agencies to protect coral reefs, mangroves, sea turtles, and other endangered species through monitoring, public education, policy advocacy, and community projects.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Conservation planning, ecological monitoring, community outreach, policy advocacy.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Marine Science.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Marine Conservation, Ecology, Environmental Policy, Community Management.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Project Assistant → Project Officer → Project Manager → Conservation Director.
            </li>
            <li value="HYDROGRAPHIC SURVEYOR">
                <b>Hydrographic Surveyor Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> A specialist in mapping the seafloor, using sonar and multibeam systems to measure underwater topography, depth, and obstacles, providing critical data for navigation safety, pipelines, ports, and ocean engineering.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Hydrographic surveying, sonar technology, GIS mapping, data processing.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Marine Technology.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Hydrographic Surveying, Geodesy, Acoustic Positioning, Geographic Information System (GIS).
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Survey Assistant → Hydrographic Surveyor → Senior Surveyor / Project Lead.
            </li>
            <li value="ACTUARY">
                <b>Actuary Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> Actuaries are top-tier financial experts who use mathematics and statistics to assess future uncertain risks. They work in insurance and consulting firms to calculate premium rates, evaluate the adequacy of reserves, and perform risk modeling.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Risk modeling, statistical analysis, financial projections, passing actuarial exams.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Mathematics.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Actuarial Mathematics, Probability Theory, Financial Mathematics, Statistics.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Actuarial Assistant → Associate Actuary → Fellow Actuary → Chief Actuary.
                <br/><b>Industries:</b> Insurance, Finance, Consulting.
                <br/><b>Salary:</b> RM 7,000 - RM 25,000/month.
            </li>
            <li value="STATISTICIAN">
                <b>Statistician Details:</b>
                <br/><b>Role:</b> The scientist who "lets data speak," applying statistical methods across industries (pharma, government, market research) to design experiments, collect and analyze data, and interpret results. Their work ensures the scientific validity and reliability of studies, from clinical trials to national censuses.
                <br/><b>Key Skills:</b> Statistical modeling, data analysis, experimental design, problem solving.
                <br/><b>Matching Majors:</b> Mathematics and Applied Mathematics.
                <br/><b>Core Courses:</b> Mathematical Statistics, Probability Theory, Regression Analysis, Experimental Design.
                <br/><b>Career Path:</b> Statistician → Biostatistician / Data Scientist → Head of Statistics Department.
            </li>

            <li>
                I don't recognize that career. Please try one of these examples:
                <br/>BACKEND DEVELOPER, DATA SCIENTIST, UX DESIGNER,
                <br/>MARINE BIOLOGIST,AUDITOR , ACTUARY.
                <br/><br/>
            </li>
        </condition>
    </template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>WHAT IS A *</pattern>
    <template><srai>DETAILS ABOUT <star/></srai></template>
</category>
<category>
    <pattern>TELL ME ABOUT A *</pattern>
    <template><srai>DETAILS ABOUT <star/></srai></template>
</category>
<category>
    <pattern>DESCRIBE *</pattern>
    <template><srai>DETAILS ABOUT <star/></srai></template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>CAREERS FOR * AND *</pattern>
    <template>
        <think>
            <set name="field1"><star index="1"/></set>
            <set name="field2"><star index="2"/></set>
        </think>
        <!-- This redirects to a simpler, more robust matching system below -->
        <srai><get name="field1"/> AND <get name="field2"/> CAREERS</srai>
    </template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>* CAREERS FOR * AND *</pattern>
    <template><srai>CAREERS FOR <star index="2"/> AND <star index="3"/></srai></template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>ART AND SCIENCE CAREERS</pattern>
    <template>
        <b>Art + Science Interdisciplinary Careers:</b><br/>
        - <b>Scientific Illustrator:</b> Creates accurate visual representations of scientific concepts. (Skills: Scientific knowledge + Artistic techniques)<br/>
        - <b>Sound Engineer:</b> Designs audio systems using acoustic principles. (Skills: Physics of sound + Audio technology)<br/>
        - <b>Conservation Technologist:</b> Applies technology to art restoration and preservation. (Skills: Materials science + Digital imaging)<br/>
        <b>Academic Path Example:</b> Combine Digital Media Technology with Physics/Biology.
    </template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>SCIENCE AND ART CAREERS</pattern>
    <template><srai>ART AND SCIENCE CAREERS</srai></template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>ART AND BUSINESS CAREERS</pattern>
    <template>
        <b>Art + Business Interdisciplinary Careers:</b><br/>
        - <b>Art Market Analyst:</b> Evaluates artwork investment potential and market trends. (Skills: Art valuation + Financial analysis)<br/>
        - <b>Creative Director:</b> Leads creative teams in commercial projects. (Skills: Artistic vision + Project management)<br/>
        - <b>Entertainment Producer:</b> Manages production of creative content for profit. (Skills: Storytelling + Budgeting)<br/>
        <b>Academic Path Example:</b> Combine Advertising/Design with E-commerce/Finance.
    </template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>BUSINESS AND ART CAREERS</pattern>
    <template><srai>ART AND BUSINESS CAREERS</srai></template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>BUSINESS AND SCIENCE CAREERS</pattern>
    <template>
        <b>Business + Science Interdisciplinary Careers:</b><br/>
        - <b>Pharma Product Manager:</b> Guides drug development from lab to market. (Skills: Scientific knowledge + Market analysis)<br/>
        - <b>Environmental Consultant:</b> Advises businesses on sustainable practices. (Skills: Environmental science + Cost-benefit analysis)<br/>
        - <b>Biotech Investment Analyst:</b> Evaluates investment opportunities in life sciences. (Skills: Scientific literacy + Financial modeling)<br/>
        <b>Academic Path Example:</b> Combine Biotechnology/Chemistry with International Business.
    </template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>SCIENCE AND BUSINESS CAREERS</pattern>
    <template><srai>BUSINESS AND SCIENCE CAREERS</srai></template>
</category>

<!-- CAREER PREPARATION -->
<category>
    <pattern>RESUME HELP</pattern>
    <template>
        <b>Resume Building Guide:</b>
        <br/>1. <b>Structure:</b> Contact Info → Summary → Education → Experience → Skills.
        <br/>2. <b>Experience Section:</b> Use action verbs (e.g., Developed, Managed, Implemented) and quantify achievements (e.g., "Increased efficiency by 15%").
        <br/>3. <b>Skills:</b> Separate technical skills (e.g., Python, Java, Figma) from soft skills (e.g., Leadership, Communication).
        <br/><i>Tip: Keep it to one page for entry-level roles. Tailor it for each job application!</i>
        <br/><br/>
        <random>
            <li>
                <b>Resume Quick Tip:</b> Use a clean, professional format with consistent fonts.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Resume Quick Tip:</b> Proofread carefully for any typos or grammatical errors.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Resume Quick Tip:</b> Highlight projects and technical skills for tech roles.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Resume Quick Tip:</b> Emphasize internships and analytical abilities for business roles.
            </li>
        </random>
        <br/>For personalized feedback, you can contact the CAREER CENTER SERVICES.
    </template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>INTERVIEW PREPARATION</pattern>
    <template>
        <b>Interview Prep Steps:</b>
        <br/>1. <b>Research:</b> Understand the company, its products, culture, and recent news.
        <br/>2. <b>Prepare Stories:</b> Use the STAR method (Situation, Task, Action, Result) to structure answers for behavioral questions.
        <br/>3. <b>Technical Prep:</b> For tech roles, practice on platforms like LeetCode. For business roles, review case studies.
        <br/>4. <b>Ask Questions:</b> Prepare thoughtful questions to ask the interviewer, such as "What does a typical day look like in this role?" or "How does this team contribute to the company's goals?".
        <br/><br/>
        <random>
            <li>
                <b>Interview Day Tip:</b> Dress professionally, even for online interviews.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Interview Day Tip:</b> Practice your self-introduction (your "elevator pitch").
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>Interview Day Tip:</b> Send a thank-you note via email within 24 hours after the interview.
            </li>
        </random>
        <br/>The Career Services Office offers mock interviews.
    </template>
</category>

<category>
    <pattern>CAREER CENTER SERVICES</pattern>
    <template>
        <b>XMUM Career Services Office 📚</b>
        <br/>📍 <b>Location:</b> Room B1 #107, Career Services Office, XMU Malaysia Campus
        <br/>⏰ <b>Hours:</b> Monday–Friday, 8:30am–5:30pm
        <br/>📞 <b>Contact:</b> careerservices@xmu.edu.my | 03‑8705 5151
        <br/><br/><b>Key Services Offered:</b>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Resume &amp; Portfolio Guidance:</b> Get expert help to craft a professional resume, LinkedIn profile, and e-portfolio.</li>
            <li><b>Interview Preparation:</b> Access mock interview practice, training on techniques, and personalized feedback.</li>
            <li><b>Job &amp; Internship Portal:</b> Login with your XMUM student ID to access 2,000+ opportunities.</li>
            <li><b>Industry Talks &amp; Career Series:</b> Engage with employers and alumni through monthly events.</li>
        </ul>
        <br/>Feel free to visit or email them to schedule a session!
    </template>
</category>

<!-- User-friendly synonyms for core functions -->
<category><pattern>HOW TO WRITE RESUME</pattern><template><srai>RESUME HELP</srai></template></category>
<category><pattern>CV HELP</pattern><template><srai>RESUME HELP</srai></template></category>
<category><pattern>MOCK INTERVIEW</pattern><template><srai>INTERVIEW PREPARATION</srai></template></category>
<category><pattern>JOB INTERVIEW TIPS</pattern><template><srai>INTERVIEW PREPARATION</srai></template></category>
<category><pattern>CAREER OFFICE</pattern><template><srai>CAREER CENTER SERVICES</srai></template></category>

<category>
    <pattern>*</pattern>
    <template>
        <random>
            <li>Sorry, I didn't understand that. You can ask me things like "What careers for software engineering?" or "Details about a data scientist."</li>
            <li>I'm not sure how to answer that. Try asking about majors, career options, or resume help.</li>
            <li>I can help with career-related questions. For example, try "What majors are in engineering?" or "How to write resume"</li>
        </random>
    </template>
</category>

</aiml>
